(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ
Sakura Miko 1st Live Made-to-Order Goods
35Pのみんなからのお祝いメッセージ
Celebratory messages from all the 35P (fans).
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention / ご来場のお客様へ
Attention / To our audience members
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ①
Sakura Miko 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 1
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ②
Sakura Miko 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 2
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ③
Sakura Miko 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 3
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ④
Sakura Miko 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods 4
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ ① 応援セット
Exclusive Pre-order Goods ① Support Set
受注生産グッズ ② 35Pはっぴセット
Exclusive Pre-order Goods ② 35P Happi Set
受注生産グッズ ③ ブランケット / チャーム
Exclusive Pre-order Goods ③ Blanket / Charm
受注生産グッズ ④ スタンド / タペストリー etc.
Exclusive Pre-order Goods ④ Stand / Tapestry etc.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To the audience members
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ①
応援セット
Sakura Miko 1st Live Made-to-order Goods 1
Support Set
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ②
Sakura Miko 1st Live Made-to-order Goods 2
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ③
Sakura Miko 1st Live Made-to-order Goods 3
さくらみこ 1st Live 受注生産グッズ ④
Sakura Miko 1st Live Made-to-order Goods 4
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Please wait a moment until the start of the performance.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Attention
To the visiting audience
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance
Cheering loudly is OK
受注生産グッズ ①
応援セット
35P ライト / タスキ風タオル / T シャツ
特典：リストバンド
Made-to-order Goods 1
Support Set
35P Light / Sash-style Towel / T-shirt
Bonus: Wristband
受注生産グッズ ②
35P はっぴ / 35P ライト
T シャツ / タスキ風タオル
Made-to-order Goods 2
35P Happi / 35P Light
T-shirt / Sash-style Towel
受注生産グッズ ③
たい焼きポーチ付きブランケット
モチーフチャーム
Made-to-order Goods 3
Blanket with Taiyaki Pouch
Motif Charm
受注生産グッズ ④
アクリルペンライトスタンド
タペストリー
クリアファイル & 缶バッジセット
Made-to-order Goods 4
Acrylic Penlight Stand
Tapestry
Clear File & Tin Badge Set
さくらみこ 1st Live “flower fantasista!”
Sakura Miko 1st Live “flower fantasista!”
むかしむかし
Once upon a time...
むかしむかし、電脳世界から神様は...
Once upon a time, from the cyber world, God...
...生まれたばかりの世界を豊かにするため、
...in order to enrich the newly born world,
神の使いを創造しました。
He created a divine messenger.
名を、さくらみこ。
Her name: Sakura Miko.
神様のお使いはそっちのけで、
Putting her duties as a messenger aside,
アイドルに出会い、あこがれました。
She encountered idols and came to admire them.
でもさいしょは、うまくはいきませんでした。
But at first, things didn't go well.
そこに、みこを支えようとみこぴーが集まってきました。
Then, the Mikopi gathered to support Miko.
それからたくさんの仲間に出会い、
After that, she met many companions,
努力し、頑張り続け、
Worked hard, persevered,
そして、みこは...
And then, Miko...
そんな私の夢は...
My dream is...
アイドルになることです！
...to become an idol!
にゃはろー！
Nyahallo!
みこのその一歩！
This is Miko's first step!
みんな、いくぞー！
Everyone, let's go!
ねぇ　思い出した歌
Hey, a song I remembered
そっと　涙した日は
On days when I quietly shed tears
さあ　数えてみようか
Come on, shall we try counting
これまで起こした奇跡を
The miracles we've made so far
ひとつ　止まらない足で
One, with feet that won't stop
ふたつ　超えていく夢も
Two, even the dreams we go beyond
みっつ　繋がる絆は
Three, the bonds that connect us
君と広げてきたんだよ
Are what I've spread with you
何度でも　咲き誇り
Blooming proudly again and again
続いていく物語
The story that continues
まだ見たことのない　景色を探しに行こう
Let's go find the scenery we haven't seen yet
花ひとつずつが　小さくてもほら
Even if each flower is small, see
支え合えたら　桜になれるよ
If we support each other, we can become cherry blossoms
僕らが繋いだ　大きな希望は
The great hope that we connected
これからも　春風になって　満ちていくのさ
Will become the spring breeze and continue to fill the air
ひとつ　涙こぼれたら
One, if a tear falls
ふたつ　両手を叩いて
Two, clap your hands
みっつ　数えて始めよう　君といれば大丈夫
Count to three and let's begin, with you it's okay
弱音と本音で泣いたり
Crying with complaints and true feelings
諦めかけたルートも
Even the routes I almost gave up on
塗り替えて笑い合えた　ずっと強くなれたんだ
We repainted and laughed together, I've become stronger
枝ひとつずつじゃ　心許なくても　ほら
Even if each branch is precarious, see
支え合えたら　桜樹になれるよ
If we support each other, we can become a cherry tree
手と手を合わせ　形は花びら
Putting hand to hand, the shape is a petal
この気持ち　言葉すら超えて　届けるのさ
I'll deliver this feeling, even beyond words
冴えない私を　好きになってくれたこと
The fact that you came to like someone like me
これからも後悔なんて　させないから見ててね
I won't let you regret it, so keep watching me
意地を張ってた　あの日よりも　強く大きくなったでしょ？
I've grown stronger and bigger than that stubborn day, right?
次は君の　支えになりたいから
Because next, I want to be your support
空に願う星　涙をあずけて
Wishing on the stars in the sky, entrusting my tears
そろそろ僕も　一歩踏み出すよ
It's about time I too take a step forward
僕らが育てた　大きな希望は　ほら
The great hope that we nurtured, see
こんなにも　色とりどりのような　場所になったよ
It has become such a vibrant and colorful place
ラララ...
La la la...
最後まで見逃すなよ！
Don't miss a thing until the very end!
盛り上がって行くぞー！
Let's get fired up!
にゃっはろーわーるど さぁ行こう
Nyahallo World, let's go!
エリートと舐めんないざ登壇
Don't look down on an elite, entering the stage now
みこち！みこち！
Mikochi! Mikochi!
配信だけじゃもう集まれーい！
Gather up, not just for the stream!
102まで愛を叫んで育ってこのアホ毛
Screaming love until 102, grow this ahoge
ついに来たぞ 有明アリーナ！
We finally made it, Ariake Arena!
会場のみんなも 画面の前のみんなも
Everyone in the venue, everyone in front of the screen
全員声出していけー！
Everyone, let me hear your voices!
わがった、わがんないの繰り返し
Repeating "I get it", "I don't get it"
ケチャして行くぜ ポジな人生
Cheering with Kecha, a positive life
エリートな目論見外れるんで あんたらの顔前立って未来
Elite plans go awry, standing before your faces, the future
デモレカトカをしてんのね そんなこんちゃ
I'm doing a demo or whatever, that's what's up
今に見てろ咲きそうなのね アニメーションやアップパンチ
Just you wait, I'm about to bloom, animation or up-punch
全人類盛り上がって はばたくバタフライ
All humanity, get hyped! Fluttering butterfly
毎日バラ色見い出した 100人が無限色だ
Finding rosy days every day, 100 people are infinite colors
にゃっはろーわーるど さぁ行こう 水平線突き上げろ
Nyahallo World, let's go! Thrust up the horizon
はい！
Yes!
キミにはキミの乳酸菌載せて
Carrying your own lactic acid bacteria
にゃっはろーわーるど さぁ行こう エリートと舐めんないざ登壇
Nyahallo World, let's go! Don't look down on an elite, entering the stage now
はい！
Yes!
配信だけじゃもう集まれ
Gather up, not just for the stream
白熱まで想いを燃やして つたえに地上中
Burning thoughts until white heat, spreading all over the world
届かなくたって頑張るから
I'll do my best even if it doesn't reach
光ってほら虹色だね 一途なマイスタイル
Look, it's shining in rainbow colors. My single-minded style.
みこみこにー！
Miko Miko Ni!
アイエンビーシー 十五円ねえ こんちあーじゃん！我ら三身
I-N-V-C, 15 yen, right? Konchi-ah, right? We are three bodies
恩年全開 パンデミック悩み越くって頭もポンにして
Full age at full throttle, pandemic! Get over your worries and make your head 'pon' too
めげないしょげない 痛くないね 荒んた世の中も諦めんな
Don't be discouraged, don't be downcast, it doesn't hurt. Don't give up on this desolate world.
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
右見て左見て 個性残してみない？
Looking right, looking left, why not leave your individuality?
これが王座のホルモン 撒き散らせ
This is the hormone of the throne, spread it around
テコ入れ人生無茶苦種で 猛攻で馬鹿だね
Revised life is a mess, a relentless onslaught, how foolish
全人類盛り上がって はばたくバタフライ
All humanity, get hyped! Fluttering butterfly
咲かせた曲がり角 導き出そう 今人生真っ只中
The corner where we bloomed, let's lead the way. Now in the middle of life.
あしたもうたおう この場所 寂しい思いさせないよ
Let's sing tomorrow too, in this place. I won't let you feel lonely.
みこ田みこPみんなで作る 独壇場なんで！
Miko-ta, Miko-P, everyone making it, because it's our specialty!
にゃっはろーわーるど さぁ行こう ちっちゃい体声上げろ
Nyahallo World, let's go! Small body, raise your voice!
はい！
Yes!
汗もしたたる いい女なんで
Because I'm a fine woman, even dripping with sweat
にゃっはろーわーるど さぁ行こう エリートと舐めんないざ登壇
Nyahallo World, let's go! Don't look down on an elite, entering the stage now
はい！
Yes!
配信だけじゃもう集まれ
Gather up, not just for the stream
白熱まで騒ごうわらって 痛めねぇ感情
Let's make a fuss until white heat, laughing, feelings that don't hurt
もっと遊んでごめん越しだって ハイタッチめちゃくちゃ笑ったっていいから
Play more, even if it's over an apology. High-fives, it's okay to laugh like crazy.
光ってほら虹色だね 一途なマイスタイル
Look, it's shining in rainbow colors. My single-minded style.
一緒に行こう ひとりとずっとな名前呼ぶよ
Let's go together. I'll call out each and every name forever.
サンキュー！
Thank you!
わぁー... はぁ、はぁ... みんなー！
Wow... *panting* Everyone!
挨拶行きますよー！
Here comes the greeting!
にゃっはろぉぉぉー！
Nyahallooooo!
はい！ということでね、35P、みこと一緒に有明来たぞー！
Yes! So, 35P, I came to Ariake with Miko!
いやちょっと、みんなの声がすごすぎる。
Wow, everyone's voices are too much.
まじで、みんなの声が、すごーいぞー！
Seriously, everyone's voices are amazing!
はい！ということで、さくらみこ 1stソロライブ
Yes! So, Sakura Miko's 1st Solo Live
「flower fantasista!」が始まりましたー！
"flower fantasista!" has begun!
みんな、来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming!
後ろのみんなも見えてるよね？
I can see everyone in the back too, right?
見えてるよ！見えてるよ！
I see you! I see you!
「みんな見えとるよ～！」
"I can see everyone!"
「イェー！」
"Yeah!"
「後ろにい～っぱい35Pがいます！」
"There are so many 35P in the back!"
「はい！ということで、もう本当にね、」
"Yes! And so, it's really..."
「ついに来てしまったという高揚感、」
"...an exhilarating feeling that this day has finally come,"
「そして、もうなんか言葉にできない感動、」
"...and a moving experience that I can't put into words."
「もうそれでだんだんだんだん口がパサパサに」
"My mouth is getting dryer and dryer"
「なってきました！」
"from all the excitement!"
「みんな、ありがとう～！」
"Everyone, thank you!"
「うえ～～ん」
"Waaaah..."
「ちょっと待って、泣かせないで、」
"Wait a minute, don't make me cry."
「まだ早い！まだ早いんじゃな！」
"It's too early! It's too early for that!"
「え、でもさ、でもさ、泣いてる35Pおるよね？」
"Wait, but, but, there are some 35P crying, right?"
「泣いとるよな？」
"You are crying, aren't you?"
「そりゃそうだ。」
"I guess that's natural."
「だってこんなにエリートなみこが、」
"Because such an elite Miko"
「こんなに素晴らしく咲き誇ってる、」
"is blooming so beautifully"
「有明アリーナとかいうでっかい場所に！」
"in this huge place called Ariake Arena!"
「ということで、ということでってよく言っちゃうよ、」
"And so... I say 'and so' a lot,"
「7年目、ついに、」
"in my 7th year, finally..."
「ついにソロライブ開催が、」
"...the solo live performance is..."
「あ、決定してない、決定してなくて、」
"Oh, not decided... it wasn't decided..."
「えっと、開催したー！」
"well, it's happening now!"
「35Pも一緒に」
"35P, let's all together"
「どーおーくさん」
"bloom as much"
「咲き誇って、」
"as we possibly can,"
「最高の景色を見ましょう！」
"and see the best scenery!"
「みこのことを見つけてくれた、」
"To everyone who found Miko,"
「もう全部の人に、」
"to every single person,"
「今日は都合でリアタイはできないよって人にも、」
"even to those who can't watch in real-time today,"
「全部全部、関わってくれた人、」
"to every single person who was involved,"
「みんなにこの最高のライブをみんなで届けようね！」
"let's deliver this best live performance to everyone!"
「一緒に最高のライブ過ごそうね！」
"Let's spend the best live together!"
「えー、そしてね、無料チラ見せっていうのをやっています。」
"And also, we're doing a free sneak peek."
「TikTokとかYouTubeとか、」
"On TikTok and YouTube..."
「でも、もうすぐ終わっちゃうかも、わかんないけどね！」
"But it might end soon, I don't know!"
「そのために早めに買ってね！買えーー！！」
"So buy it soon! Buy it!!"
「みんな買ってって言って。買って、買って！」
"Everyone say 'Buy it.' Buy it, buy it!"
「はい、そして、スクショや感想はハッシュタグ、」
"Yes, and for screenshots and impressions, use the hashtag"
「#咲き誇るみこちをつけて投稿してください！」
"#咲き誇るみこち when you post!"
「それではみんな、」
"Well then everyone,"
「次の曲いくぞー！」
"let's go to the next song!"
「ついてこれるのかー！？」
"Can you keep up!?"
「 Elite !! 」
"Elite!!"
にゃっほ～！さくらみこでーす！
Nyaho! It's Sakuramiko!
かちこまっちゃってください
Please get "Kachikoma'd"
ピース・コンプリート！えーい！
Peace Complete! Ay!
「 Elite !! 」
"Elite!!"
さあ、もっと鳴らしちゃって
Come on, let's make more noise
始めちゃえ
Let's get started
今日もキメてええやろ？挑戦者
Deciding today's good too, right? Challenger
ちゅちょは厳禁　足踏みしてないで
Hesitation is strictly forbidden, don't just step in place
一緒にせーのでもっと前に行こう　ね？
Let's go further forward together on "one-two", okay?
さあ、なんとかなっちゃえ
Come on, it'll work out somehow
飛び込んで
Jump right in
なんたってジッとしたって人生は冒険だ
After all, even if you stay still, life is an adventure
こんがらがったら　またわかんないと
If you get tangled up, if you don't understand again
未知なりは困難だ！難難だ！勝負だ！
The unknown is difficult! Hard, hard! It's a showdown!
メソメソしちゃって　気持ちに「待った」しちゃって
Moping around, putting a "wait" on your feelings
ほら一体全体どうした？
Look, what on earth happened?
「 君たちには 」
"For you all"
涙は似合わないね！
Tears don't suit you!
大大大冒険に飛び出そうぜ　いいじゃん
Let's jump into a big, big, big adventure, it's fine
大大大失敗も重ねて成長して
Growth comes even from making big, big, big mistakes
ハッピーなみこしで
With a happy Mikoshi
君と笑い話にしよう
Let's make it a funny story together
大大大問題を吹き飛ばせ！
Blow away the big, big, big problems!
いつか大大大大団円の素敵な結末へ
Someday to a wonderful conclusion of a big grand finale
ピースを繋げて進め
Connect the pieces and move forward
限界もノーノー！
Limits are also no-no!
「 ソロライブ たのしんでこぇ！！ 」
"Have fun at the solo live!!"
あちこち間違ってる　またボケも掘ってる
Mistakes here and there, digging a hole with another blunder
満身創痍だって持ってる　なんか違ってる
Even if battered, still got it, something feels different
ぶっちゃけ有識者のみなさまに感謝してます
Frankly, I'm grateful to all you experts
ナイス・コメ！待ってゼンゼ！
Nice comment! Wait, not at all!
ウジウジしちゃって　心にロックしちゃって
Fretting around, locking up your heart
ほらだんだんだんだんどうした？
Look, what happened bit by bit?
笑顔が足りてないね
You don't have enough smiles, do you?
大大大大好きじゃ済まさない　いいじゃんね
Just "love, love, love, love" isn't enough, it's fine, right?
大大大満足のその上の感動を
An emotion beyond just "satisfaction, satisfaction, satisfaction"
もっと欲しがっちゃって　ほかに贅沢にいこう
Want it even more, let's go for even more luxury
全然前進したいって凹んじゃったって
Even if I get depressed wanting to move forward at all
ならば全身全霊人生最大の全力で
Then, with my whole heart and soul, the greatest effort of my life
La pa pa 三拍子に息を合わせて進め Peace Sign
La pa pa, breathe in time with the triple meter and move forward, Peace Sign
Wow Wow Wow
乗り遅れんなよ　みんな！
Don't be left behind, everyone!
Wow Wow Wow
声聴かせて！
Let me hear your voices!
Wow Wow Wow
歌声高らかに
Sing out loud and clear
ベイベイベイなんてさ　なんだかちょっと言い表せない
Bay-bay-bay, it's like, I can't quite put it into words
独りぼっちで見合てた光景は
The scenery I looked at all by myself
今はきっとあなたと冒険してる
Is surely an adventure with you now
大大大大大大大大
Big big big big big big big big big
大大大大好きじゃ収まらない
Just "love, love, love, love" won't fit
だから最大レベルにガチの全力で
So, with serious full power at the maximum level
La pa pa 踊っちゃおうぜ　ずっと大冒険
La pa pa, let's dance, it's a big adventure forever
Peace Sign
大大大問題も吹き飛ばせ
Blow away even "big, big, big" problems
いつの日か大大大団円の素敵な結末へ
Someday, to a wonderful grand finale ending
Follow me 付いてきて　進め　前代未聞　ニューワールド
Follow me, come with me, advance to an unprecedented new world
刮目しててくれ Peace Sign
Keep your eyes on me, Peace Sign
Flower Fantasista!
咲き誇るぜ　ベイベー！
I'll bloom in full glory, baby!
Oh!
Ah!
行くにぇ！
Let's go!
キュンキュンみこキュン　キュンキュンみこキュン
Kyun kyun Miko Kyun, Kyun kyun Miko Kyun
君にみこキュン
Miko Kyun for you
衣装チェンジだにぇ！
It's a costume change!
みんな、キュンキュンしてにぇ！
Everyone, please feel the "kyun"!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
Sakura Miko 1st Live flower fantasista!
2024.10.26 sat ARIAKE ARENA #咲き誇るみこち
2024.10.26 Sat ARIAKE ARENA #SakihoruMikochi
無料パートは終了いたしました。
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.